I'm also a bit nervous because I've never driven a caramel before.
Oh, I see.
It's your first time, with the video.
It's true.
Real...
I'm a bit nervous.
Where do you want to go?
No, I want to go to the beach.
The sea?
Yeah, the ocean?
The water.
Do you know Odaiba Seaside Park?
No, I don't.
Oh, that sandy place?
This one.
I've never been there.
Let's try Odaiba Seaside Park.
What, here, oh, oh, that's not a station?
Well, it's not so much the destination that's important.
It's more like, "Let's talk while we drive.
That's true.
Tokyo Night Drive.
It's a Tokyo night drive.
Let's just leave it at that.
Okay, let's go.
Thank you for listening to the music. Thank you for listening to the music.
I'm off. - Mm! Okay.
Aaah!
Is that what I think it is?
Soft serve ice cream.
Waku, that's it, waffles.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Tastes like...
Delicious.
Next time, melon bread biscuits.
I think you should try some of these.
I've just bought these.
I'm going to take these to the Canadian shop.
I don't think we should eat them.
I shouldn't eat them while I'm driving.
You shouldn't eat it while you're driving.
Yum!
Melon bread biscuits!
That's all I've heard for a while now.
They're my favourite.
They're high in calories.
But it's the first time I've seen them.
It's a bit sudden, isn't it?
You're getting carried away.
I'm sorry, the first time we met was...
When was the first time we met?
Almost.
Almost... because... because...
When did Ryota and I first meet?
Ryota was doing it first.
Battle.
You see, that's why...
The day we first met...
I came into the office.
I joined Ebidan.
And, um...
That Ebidan lesson started.
The first day I went there
I saw Ryota for the first time at the lesson.
And at that time, the dance shoes I bought and the dance shoes Ryota bought were the same.
It was really awkward.
I saw that Ryota was wearing light blue ones.
That was the first time I saw him.
What? !
I thought those were the coolest shoes in the world.
You're right, they were cool.
I thought they were the coolest shoes in the world.
I went and bought a white air hose.
I went and got a white air hose, you know, on order.
Oh, my God, I'm wearing the same brand.
I thought you were a good dancer from then on.
Oh, you were good then?
I mean, you know what?
I used to do ballet, so it was my first time doing hip-hop.
I was so nervous.
Did you talk to him then? You didn't? I was doing ballet, so I was really nervous about my first hip-hop gig.
Did you talk to him then? You didn't?
Tell me what?
To Kaname here.
Kaname and I...
You didn't talk? Because after I met Ryota.
I started talking to him pretty late.
That's right.
You didn't have a meeting with some of them?
We had a few people over.
It was really just the two of us.
Because we got on so mysteriously.
Suddenly we were friends for a day.
We'd never been strangers before.
Yeah, right.
Why was that?
We didn't go shopping for glasses together.
Oh! We did!
What, did you go to Ikebukuro together?
There's this really cool guy who's famous for glasses.
I was really into glasses.
And I wanted to buy some glasses too.
But I was like, "Okay, I'll go with you.
Oh, I see. We weren't close then, were we? We didn't get along, but we're going together.
We didn't get on, but we're going together.
Go on, then.
I'm coming.
He's gone.
He bought some weird stuff.
He bought the weirdest thing.
Black ones with little lenses.
It's the best I've ever seen.
They're 10 yen.
When I said they looked good on me, we both said we wouldn't wear them at all.
We don't wear them. We haven't worn them since that day.
Then we were in the same group at the Battle Boys in Tokyo.
And we both noticed that I talked more than we thought we would.
We became friends on the way home.
Yes, well, we talked a lot, and we got to know each other on the way home.
Yes, we talked a lot.
We talked about work all the time. We talked about our dreams.
It wasn't so much that we became friends in private, but that we went shopping for glasses.
We went to buy glasses.
We were both working towards the same thing.
That's what I'm trying to say.
After you debuted, the two of you talked a lot about this group, what it would be like to be in it.
The form at that time was Lanner and Mania's mv, which we always said we wanted to do, right?
That's what we always said we wanted to do.
And now I'm the leader.
And I'm the dance leader.
That's right.
That's true.
That's what I think.
It's a mystery.
We're all connected, aren't we?
Words and spirits are amazing.
No, it's a real thing.
No, seriously, it's true.
Want some?
No, give it to me.
Melon bread biscuits.
Oh, I had the, the milk one.
This one, they say it's good, the melon bread biscuit.
They're good, but...
Well, milk.
Good, good.
The milk, you know, tastes like corn.
It's good.
It's good. It's good for sales.
Open it.
Thank you very much.
The moment you turn 20.
You know what I was thinking?
I was, you know, it was taken pretty seriously.
I was thinking about the transition between 19 and 20.
No, but it's... it's... it's more than I thought.
It's kind of poofy.
Do you want to clarify?
Oh, it's very much like that.
I was like, "I'm 20.
I see.
Since I turned 20.
And when I turned 20, I could drink alcohol.
With both of us.
It was your dream, wasn't it?
Let's go out together.
It's on the right, and 20 metres further on, it's on the left.
We went together, didn't we?
Yes, we did.
We're not the type of people who get together, you know?
Quite the opposite.
We ended up chatting with the other girls in the group and having a lot of fun.
Don't you talk about work all the time? We talk about work all the time?
Basically, I don't talk about work.
That's cool.
About 300 metres away.
I'm feeling good right now.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's a great night view.
It's so beautiful!
Look at this.
That's where we used to do our releases.
Dex? Oh, my God, look at this, right here, right here, right there, where we were re-leaving the building.
Dex? Dex?
Dex?
Yeah, right.
Okay, yeah.
Thank you. Thank you.
Once we've done this.
I said I wanted to see the sea.
They brought me to the sea.
The sea, we've arrived.
Oho!
Oh, it's so
It's amazing.
I've never been here before.
Oh, my God.
What, do you have a phone downstairs?
Do you want to go to the SMA?
You're going?
What about the weather?
No, it's pretty much a level playing field.
But I thought we'd never get on.
You mean, like, on the flip side?
I don't know.
Oh, well, you're right.
You don't seem like the kind of girl I'd get along with.
Well, I get that a lot.
I get that a lot, too.
So maybe...
That's not true.
No, it's not like that.
It's just that we've both got better at it, but we're shy.
That's why we don't talk to each other.
I thought we'd never get on.
I thought we'd never get on, but now that we might be the same...
I don't think we'll ever get on.
I don't think we'll ever have any contact with each other.
I thought we'd never be together, and then I realised we'd be the same. - From now on. - If we're never going to be together...
I don't think that's weird.
- I don't think that's weird.
- Right now.
- You're the one who's changing so much in Cocos Lane.
Me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. You're about 50 times more reliable.
Really? - Yeah.
- Yeah.
I'm so happy.
I don't know.
That's why...
I don't feel like a royal leader.
You know what?
He hasn't changed that much.
That's what I like about you.
It fits my impression.
All the members more than me.
You don't have to think about anything just because you're the leader.
Like that.
We talked about it.
That's right.
You don't have to try to be a leader.
That's what he said to me.
That's more than I can say.
Yeah, that's right.
It's not a group where someone says, "Let's go" or "Let's do it properly".
It's a group that notices the atmosphere around it and moves together.
I kept my mouth shut.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
But when we do it, it's like...
We'll tighten up, but we'll also tighten up properly, and that'll give Carle a shape.
I really feel it.
That's it, this is the leader.
Gaziota is the dance leader, and this is the group.
I don't know what a dance leader does, to be honest.
No, I don't.
In terms of leading the performance.
I don't have to say anything.
Jota does it for me.
I don't know...
I don't know.
I think Jota's changed.
I mean, she can say a lot more now than she used to.
Before...
I'd point out that Jota probably has something he wants to say.
I'd say, "Yes, you can," even if I had to choose the words.
Now I don't have that anymore, so I'd ask him about it a lot.
And now Ryota's telling me.
But he's...
I can see how he still thinks about it.
I can tell.
We're probably both...
There are moments when we both think each other's thoughts are real.
We definitely talked about that when we went out for dinner before.
It was right after we made our debut.
The prototype of what you are now was already formed.
So it just happened the way it did.
Well, that's true.
When I think about it, it really feels like it's just beginning.
This year, I've finally got all the observers together.
I really want to go with you. You've been doing this since the Corona Disaster.
That's where it all started from.
The distance between you and the participants was really long, wasn't it?
It's true.
They come to our shows, but...
But without the broadcasters...
You can hear their voices.
You can see their smiling faces without the masks.
That...
That's all it takes.
It makes such a difference.
I know.
I have to work hard.
Yeah, you're right. We have to work hard.
You're the one who's probably watching the most.
We're the same age, same age, same circumstances.
All the same age.
You don't even know it, just let it affect you.
That's true.
The way we grow up.
Hobbies, work...
Because I'm still in dance lessons.
I still get frustrated when I can't do the steps
I feel frustrated when I can't do it.
There's a genre called hip-hop.
genre.
From the very beginning, when we first met.
I got the impression that you can dance.
You're someone who has something that you don't have.
But I've seen...
I think it's a pretty good play.
Plays?
All thespians and thespians.
I mean, they're all in the local section.
But you see the plays of the Tokiwaki members.
It's not the most serious thing to watch, but...
It's embarrassing, but it makes me happy.
I'm so glad to see it. I feel like I have to do my best.
I understand, it's very windy.
I don't care what it's like.
I get it.
We're comrades-in-arms, rivals...
But most of all, I'm a member.
I'm sure I'll be able to reaffirm one more thing today.
Hey.
Shall we go?
I'll drive.
Let's go.
Drive safe.
That was fun.
Let's get out of here.
We're going home.
We're going home... we're going home... we've had a great summer... we're going home... we're going home...
I'm looking forward to summer.
I really have to work hard this year.
I know I say that every year.
How many times do we say...
We've got to work hard.
We say it every day.
Destination ends in 30 metres.
I don't know.
It's true, 30 metres ahead is the end of the perimeter.
If that's true...
I wish we could both talk about the future.
You'll be turning left shortly.
Eventually.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Around the destination.
Beautiful.
That's all we've got to talk about.
Because that's all we talk about.
Even in private, in the end, because that's the only thing that comes out, even in private.
In the end.
That's the way it is, isn't it?
It was just the two of us talking as usual.
Well, yeah...
That's fine.
Take a picture of that.
Well...
It's like, let's just go for it.
I'll do my best. Reality.
Keep up the good work.
Long may it continue.